alpssocial.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy - AlpsSocial - The World's FREE Financial Opportunity Marketplace

This Privacy Policy sets out how Alps Networks uses and protects any information that you give Alps Networks when you use this website. If you continue to browse or use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following Privacy Policy, which together with our Terms and Conditions govern Alps Networks's relationship with you in relation to this website.

Please review carefully the entire website's Privacy Policy before agreeing to it. By viewing or using this website or any part of it, you agree to the complete Privacy Policy of this website.

The term "Alps Networks", "this website","the website", "us" or "we" refers to the owner of the website. The term "you" refers to the user or viewer of the website.   
Alps Networks is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected as provided in this Privacy Policy. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Alps Networks may change this policy from time to time by updating this page, and by providing any information to Alps Networks you're accepting such changes. You should check this page from time to time for any changes. This policy is effective from December 18, 2014.

What we collect  
We may collect the following information:   
• Personal identification details, such as name, age, etc.  
• Contact information including email address.  
• Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.   
• Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

What we do with the information we gather.  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:   
• Internal record keeping.  
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.   
• We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.   
• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.   
• We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

Security  
We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Further more, our employees and third party service providers have access to your non-public personal information only on a "need to know" basis.

We follow industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

However, To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event shall Alps Networks, its affiliates, or their respective officers, directors, shareholders, employees and agents be liable for any damages, liability, claims, expenses and costs, incurred by or as a result from any breach or negligence regarding your information, and Alps Networks shall have no duty of confidentiality regarding personal or other information submitted on the website.

How we use cookies  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you. As an individual the web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:   
• In the settings page, 'Profile' tab, control the information shared.   
• In the settings page, 'Notifications' tab, choose the notification types sent to your email.  
• In your settings area, control which information to share per each account.  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.

Legal requirement to disclose information  
Alps Networks may be required to disclose or provide your information including but not limited to in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against actual or threatened legal claims.

In addition Alps Networks may disclose or provide any of your information if Alps Networks will find appropriate to do so, including but not limited to, when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action, regarding illegal activities or activities which we believe give rise to legal liability to us or third parties, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Alps Networks terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

Miscellaneous  
In the event that any provision of this Privacy Policy is held unenforceable, the validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions will not be affected, and the unenforceable provision will be replaced with an enforceable provision that comes closest to the intention underlying the unenforceable provision.
